Correctional Association of New York; Records apap014
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Miscellaneous Publication Files, 1944; 1976-1979; 1982-1986; 8; 0.33 cubic ft.
  - News Bulletin, 1969; 1983-1986; 1987 (Box 1 (8-Miscellaneous Publication Files), Folder 3)
  - One Hundred Years of Faithful Service, 1944 (Box 1 (8-Miscellaneous Publication Files), Folder 4)
  - 131st Annual Report to the Legislature, 1976 (Box 1 (8-Miscellaneous Publication Files), Folder 5)
  - 132nd Annual Report to the Legislature, 1977 (Box 1 (8-Miscellaneous Publication Files), Folder 6)
  - 133rd Annual Report to the Legislature, 1978 (Box 1 (8-Miscellaneous Publication Files), Folder 7)
  - 134th Annual Report to the Legislature, 1979 (Box 1 (8-Miscellaneous Publication Files), Folder 8)
  - Price of Punishment: Public Spending for Corrections in New York, 1980 (Box 1 (8-Miscellaneous Publication Files), Folder 9)
  - Prison Population Explosion in New York State, 1982 (Box 1 (8-Miscellaneous Publication Files), Folder 10)
  - What Happens on the Inside Affects All of Us on the Outside, Undated (Box 1 (8-Miscellaneous Publication Files), Folder 11)
- Reprint Series, 1961-1975; 9; 0.99 cubic ft.
  Contains articles, papers and reports created or received by the Association and reprinted for distribution on request. Topics included are alcoholism, narcotics addiction, problems of the criminal justice system, recidivism, mental health, juveniles and crime, pornography, victimless crimes, and General Secretary reports of the Association.
  - Haapala, Kathryn.About Parole in New York State. Citizens' Inquiry on Parole and Criminal Justice, Inc., New York, 1975 August (Box 1 (9-Reprint Series), Folder 1)
  - Minucci, Patrick.Alcoholism, Substance Abuse Treatment Program Manual. New York State Department of Correctional Services, Woodbourne Correctional Facility, 1981 (Box 1 (9-Reprint Series), Folder 2)
  - Genesee Judicial process Commission.Alternatives to Incarceration, Genesee County. Educational Designs for Justice, Batavia, 1980 April 01 (Box 1 (9-Reprint Series), Folder 3)
  - American Bar Association Journal, 1976 October (Box 1 (9-Reprint Series), Folder 4)
  - Shernock, Stan K. "Bystander Response to Criminal Events: Rescue or Crime Control?"Criminal Justice Abstracts 19, No. 3, 1987 September (Box 1 (9-Reprint Series), Folder 5)
  - The Task Force for a Safer Society.A Call to the People of New York State to End Unnecessary Imprisonment: A Demand for Responsible Public Policies. NYS Council of Churches, Syracuse, 1980 August (Box 1 (9-Reprint Series), Folder 6)
  - President's Commission on Law Enforcement and Administration of Justice. The Challenge of Crime in a Free Society. US Government Printing Office, Washington, DC, 1967 February (Box 1 (9-Reprint Series), Folder 7)
  - American Correctional Association.Classification. College Park, 1981 April (Box 1 (9-Reprint Series), Folder 8)
  - Klapmuts, Nora.Community Alternatives to Prison. National Council on Crime and Delinquency, 1973 June (Box 1 (9-Reprint Series), Folder 9)
  - Coopers and Lybrand.The Cost of Incarceration in New York City. The National Council on Crime and Delinquency, Hackensack, 1978 (Box 1 (9-Reprint Series), Folder 10)
  - Community Service Society of New York.Crimes Against the Elderly. Statement for NAACP Workshop on the Urban Crisis: Minority Perspectives on Criminal Justice, St. Louis, 1977 June 29 (Box 1 (9-Reprint Series), Folder 11)
  - US Department of Justice.Criminal Victimization of New York State Residents 1974-77. Bureau of Justice Statistics, National Crime Survey Report, Washington, DC, 1980 June (Box 1 (9-Reprint Series), Folder 12)
  - US Department of Justice.Criminal Victimization Surveys in Buffalo: A National Crime Survey Report. Washington, DC, 1977 July (Box 1 (9-Reprint Series), Folder 13)
  - NYS Advisory Commission on Criminal Sanctions.Current Sentencing Practices (Part II of the Report). New York, 1982 (Box 1 (9-Reprint Series), Folder 14)
  - Klapmuts, Nora.Diversion from the Justice System. National Council on Crime and Delinquency, Hackensack, Undated (Box 1 (9-Reprint Series), Folder 15)
  - Citizens Task Force on Alternatives to Incarceration.Final Report - Phase One, 1979 September 06 (Box 1 (9-Reprint Series), Folder 16)
  - National Conference on Women and the Law, 14th Annual.Sourcebook. Washington, DC, 1983 (Box 2 (9-Reprint Series), Folder 1)
  - Campaign for Common Sense in Criminal Justice.A Human Needs Agenda: New York's Unfinished Business. New York, Undated (Box 2 (9-Reprint Series), Folder 2)
  - Legal Aid Society Prisoners' Rights Project.Index to the Law of Conditions and Practices of Pre-Trial Detention. Criminal Appeals Bureau of the Legal Aid Society of the City of New York, New York, 1978 (Box 2 (9-Reprint Series), Folder 3)
  - Prison Fellowship.Is There a Better Way? A Perspective on American Prisons. Special Counsel on Criminal Justice, Washington, DC, 1981 (Box 2 (9-Reprint Series), Folder 4)
  - National Coalition for Jail Reform.Jail is the Wrong Placed to Be for Juveniles, Public Inebriates, the Mentally Ill and Mentally Retarded. Washington, DC, Undated (Box 2 (9-Reprint Series), Folder 5)
  - American Institute of Criminal Justice.Just the Facts. American Foundation, Inc., Undated (Box 2 (9-Reprint Series), Folder 6)
  - American Correctional Association.Manual of Correctional Standards. College Park, 1966 (Box 2 (9-Reprint Series), Folder 7)
  - Board of Correction.Minimum Standards for New York City Correctional Facilities. New York, Undated (Box 2 (9-Reprint Series), Folder 8)
  - NYS Council of Churches.New York's Prisons and Jails: A Time for Decisions. Syracuse, Undated (Box 2 (9-Reprint Series), Folder 9)
  - Board of Directors.The Nondangerous Offender Should not Be Imprisoned: A Policy Statement. National Council on Crime and Delinquency, Hackensack, 1978 (Box 2 (9-Reprint Series), Folder 10)
  - Krajick, Kevin and Steve Gettinger.Overcrowded Time: Why Prisons Are So Crowded and What Can be Done. Edna McConnell Clark Foundation, New York, 1982 (Box 2 (9-Reprint Series), Folder 11)
  - Johnson, Carolyn and Marjorie Kravitz.Overcrowding in Correctional Institutions: A Selected Bibliography. National Institute of Law Enforcement and Criminal Justice, Washington, DC, 1978 February (Box 2 (9-Reprint Series), Folder 12)
  - Feins, Judith D.Partnerships for Neighborhood Crime Prevention. US Department of Justice, National Institute of Justice, Washington, DC, 1983 June (Box 3 (9-Reprint Series), Folder 1)
  - Medvene, Louis and Carol S. Whelan.Prison Health Care in New York City: A Historical Perspective. Community Service Society, New York, 1976 May (Box 3 (9-Reprint Series), Folder 2)
  - National Council on Crime and Delinquency.Prisons: The Price We Pay. Hackensack, 1978 (Box 3 (9-Reprint Series), Folder 3)
  - National Council on Crime and Delinquency.Proposed Expansion of the NYS Prison System. Hackensack, 1979 (Box 3 (9-Reprint Series), Folder 4)
  - NYS Coalition for Criminal Justice.Questions to be Considered before Further Expansion of the State Prisons. Albany, 1981 May 13 (Box 3 (9-Reprint Series), Folder 5)
  - DuBow, Fred, Edward McCabe and Gail Kaplan.Reactions to Crime: A Critical Review of the Literature. US Department of Justice, Law Enforcement Assistance Administration, National Institute of Law Enforcement and Criminal Justice, Washington, DC, 1979 November (Box 3 (9-Reprint Series), Folder 6)
  - Bureau of Justice Statistics.Report to the Nation on Crime and Justice: The Data. US Department of Justice, Washington, DC, 1983 October (Box 3 (9-Reprint Series), Folder 7)
  - NYS Commission of Correction.A Report of the Westchester County Jail Disturbance. Valhalla, July 1981, 1981 September (Box 3 (9-Reprint Series), Folder 8)
  - Knopp, Fay Honey, et. al.Researching Your Local Jail: A Citizen's Guide for Change. Education Designs for Justice and Prison Research Education Action Project of the NYS Council of Churches, Syracuse, 1981 March (Box 3 (9-Reprint Series), Folder 9)
  - Goffin Hanna, Marcia.A Review of Temporary Release Programs in New York State. New York Commission of Correction, 1978 February 28 (Box 3 (9-Reprint Series), Folder 10)
  - Rudenstine, David.The Rights of Ex-Offenders. Avon Books, New York, 1979 (Box 3 (9-Reprint Series), Folder 11)
  - US District Court, Southern District of Texas, Houston Division.David Ruiz, et al. v. W.J. Estelle, Jr., et al. Memorandum Opinion, 1972 (Box 3 (9-Reprint Series), Folder 12)
  - League of Women Voters.Seeds of Failure: A Political Review of New York State's 1967 Constitutional Convention. New York, 1973 (Box 3 (9-Reprint Series), Folder 13)
  - Rogers J.A. Sex and Race: Negro - Caucasian Mixing in All Ages and All Lands. Volume I: The Old World. J.A. Rogers Publications, New York, 1940 (Box 3 (9-Reprint Series), Folder 14)
    Book is signed by the author.
  - NYS Department of Correctional Services.Strategic Plan, 1980-85, Undated (Box 3 (9-Reprint Series), Folder 15)
  - Campaign for Common Sense in Criminal Justice.Summary: 1986 Criminal Justice Counteragenda. New York, Undated (Box 3 (9-Reprint Series), Folder 16)
  - McGann, John R., D.D.Think of Those in Prison as though You Were in Prison with Them. Address of Bishop John R. McGann, D.D. diocese of Rockville Centre to the Eastern Regional Meeting of the American Correctional Chaplains' Association, Undated (Box 3 (9-Reprint Series), Folder 17)
  - NYC Department of Correction.This Is Your New York City Department of Correction. New York, 1983 (Box 3 (9-Reprint Series), Folder 18)
  - Cory, Bruce and Stephen Gettinger.Time to Build? The Realities of Prison Construction. Edna McConnell Clark Foundation, New York, 1984 (Box 3 (9-Reprint Series), Folder 19)
  - American Bar Association Victim Witness Assistance Project.Victim/Witness Legislation: Considerations for Policymakers. Washington, DC, 1981 (Box 3 (9-Reprint Series), Folder 20)
- Foundations and Fundraising Files, 1962-1988; 10; 2.0 cubic ft.
  This series contains information about numerous philanthropic foundations from which the Association sought funding. These files were kept separate from other records created or gathered by Association staff, and contain annual reports and other items published by numerous foundations, applications for funding, and correspondence. Also included are Association staffers' and board members' manuscript lists of contacts, fundraising ideas, and internal memoranda.
  - Astor (Vincent) Foundation, 1982-1985 (Box 1 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 1)
  - Babcock (Mary Reynolds) Foundation, 1981-1985 (Box 1 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 2)
  - Baird (Winfield) Foundation, 1963-1973 (Box 1 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 3)
  - Burden (Florence V.) Foundation, 1980-1986 (Box 1 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 4)
  - Chicago Resource Center, 1984-1985 (Box 1 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 5)
  - Chrysler Corporation, 1973 (Box 1 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 6)
  - Clark (Edna McConnell) Foundation, 1982-1985 (Box 1 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 7)
  - Clark (Edna McConnell) Foundation, 1985-1987 (Box 1 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 8)
  - Clark (Robert Sterling) Foundation, 1982-1985 (Box 1 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 9)
  - Crime and Justice Foundation, 1987 (Box 1 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 10)
  - Eisenhower (Milton S.) Foundation, A Progress Report, [1988] (Box 1 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 11)
  - Erickson Educational Foundation, Newsletter, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 12)
  - Foundation Center, 1983-1985 (Box 1 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 13)
  - Ford Foundation, 1966-1973 (Box 1 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 14)
  - Friedlander (Eugene) Foundation, 1984-1985 (Box 1 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 15)
  - Foundations, 1980-1983 (Box 1 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 16)
  - Foundations, 1983-1985 (Box 1 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 17)
  - Foundations, 1987 (Box 1 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 18)
  - Foundations - Acknowledgments, 1977-1985 (Box 1 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 19)
  - Foundations - Fundraising, 1982-1983 (Box 1 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 20)
  - Foundations - General Mailing, 1984-1985 (Box 1 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 21)
  - Foundations - Reports on Criminal Justice, 1982 (Box 1 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 22)
  - Fund for the City of New York, 1981-1985 (Box 1 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 23)
  - Funding - Church, 1981-1982 (Box 1 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 24)
  - Funding - Corporate, 1982-1983 (Box 1 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 25)
  - Funding - George F. Baker Trust, 1982-1983 (Box 1 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 26)
  - Funding - Lotta M. Crabtree Trust, 1983 (Box 1 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 27)
  - Funding Requests, 1984-1986; 2 folders (Box 1 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 28)
  - Funding Sources - General, 1982 (Box 1 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 29)
  - Fundraiser - Search, 1985 (Box 1 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 30)
  - Fundraising, 1971-1979 (Box 1 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 31)
  - Fundraising - Agencies, 1974 (Box 2 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 1)
  - Fundraising - Caesar, Patricia, 1985 (Box 2 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 2)
  - Fundraising - Church Sources, 1982-1983 (Box 2 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 3)
  - Fundraising - Consultants, 1984 (Box 2 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 4)
  - Fundraising, 1976, 1974-1976 (Box 2 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 5)
  - Fundraising - Oram Group, Inc., 1976 (Box 2 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 6)
  - Goldman (Herman) Foundation, 1984 (Box 2 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 7)
  - Grant Application - Tie-lines, 1979 (Box 2 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 8)
  - Grant (William T.) Foundation, 1983-1985 (Box 2 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 9)
  - Greater New York Fund, 1962-1973 (Box 2 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 10)
  - Greater New York Fund, 1973-1977 (Box 2 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 11)
  - Greater New York Fund, 1975-1986 (Box 2 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 12)
  - Greater New York Fund, 1977-1979 (Box 2 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 13)
  - Greater New York Fund, 1979 (Box 2 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 14)
  - Greater New York Fund, 1979-1982 (Box 2 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 15)
  - Greater New York Fund/United Way, 1986 (Box 2 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 16)
  - Guggenheim (Daniel and Florence) Foundation - Report of the President, 1978-1982; 1982 (Box 2 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 17)
  - Havens Relief Fund Society, 1975-1985 (Box 2 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 18)
  - Herman (J.M.) Fund, 1982-1983 (Box 2 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 19)
  - Hochschild Fund, 1981-1984 (Box 2 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 20)
  - Ittleson Foundation, 1985 (Box 2 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 21)
  - Joint Foundation Support, 1982-1984 (Box 2 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 22)
  - MacArthur (John D. and Catharine D.) Foundation, 1978 (Box 2 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 23)
  - Metzger - Price Fund, Inc., 1982-1985 (Box 2 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 24)
  - National Community Funds, 1980-1984 (Box 2 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 25)
  - Needmor Fund, 1982-1984 (Box 2 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 26)
  - New World Foundation, 1979-1985 (Box 2 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 27)
  - New York Community Trust, 1981-1987 (Box 2 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 28)
  - New York Foundation, 1982-1983 (Box 2 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 29)
  - New York Foundation - Materials for Latino Project, 1975-1986 (Box 2 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 30)
  - New York Times Company Foundation, 1982-1983 (Box 2 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 31)
  - New York Times Company Foundation, 1984-1984 (Box 2 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 32)
  - New World Foundation, 1986 (Box 2 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 33)
  - New York Community Trust, 1986-1987 (Box 2 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 34)
  - New York Community Trust - Funding Proposal, 1986 (Box 2 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 35)
  - New York Foundation, 1987 (Box 2 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 36)
  - Norman Foundation, 1982-1984 (Box 2 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 37)
  - Norman Foundation, 1987 (Box 2 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 38)
  - Normandie Foundation, 1986 (Box 2 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 39)
  - Ottinger Foundation, 1986 (Box 2 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 40)
  - Peter Foundation, 1986 (Box 2 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 41)
  - Phelps Dodge Foundation, 1986 (Box 2 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 42)
  - Pinkerton Foundation, 1983-1985 (Box 2 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 43)
  - Printing Funding Appeals to Corporations, 1988 (Box 2 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 44)
  - Proposals - Basic Format for Writing, ca. 1985 (Box 2 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 45)
  - Prospect Hill Foundation, 1983-1985 (Box 2 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 46)
  - Prospect Hill Foundation, 1987 (Box 2 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 47)
  - Public Interest Law Foundation, 1986 (Box 2 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 48)
  - Public Welfare Foundation, 1986-1987 (Box 2 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 49)
  - Publications Funding Proposal, 1986 (Box 2 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 50)
  - Revson (Charles H.) Foundation, 1982-1985 (Box 2 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 51)
  - Revson (Charles H.) Foundation, 1987 (Box 2 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 52)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1985 (Box 2 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 53)
  - Rubin (Samuel) Foundation, 1984 (Box 2 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 54)
  - Scherman Foundation, 1982-1985 (Box 2 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 55)
  - Stone (W. Clement and Jessie V.) Foundation, Undated (Box 2 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 56)
  - Trinity Grants Programs, 1981-1985 (Box 2 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 57)
  - United Fund of Greater New York, 1972 (Box 2 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 58)
  - Van Ameringen Foundation, 1985 (Box 2 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 59)
  - Van Ameringen Foundation, 1986 (Box 2 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 60)
  - Veatch Program, 1987 (Box 2 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 61)
  - Veatch Program - Drafts, 1986-1987 (Box 2 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 62)
  - Wallach (Mary and James G.) Foundation, 1988 (Box 2 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 63)
  - Warner Communications, 1982-1987 (Box 2 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 64)
  - Warner Communications, 1987 (Box 2 (10-Foundations and Fundraising Files), Folder 65)
- Records received in, 2006 August; 11
  The following records were received from the Correctional Association of New York in August 2006, but have not yet been intellectually or physically integrated into the collection. An inventory of the records created by the staff of the Correctional Association is available.
  - (untitled) Indenture regarding building purchase James J. Slevin, Register, 1887 (Inventory 1)
  - (untitled) note re: mortgage Eugene Smith, Secretary of Prison Association Executive Committee, 1900 (Inventory 2)
  - (untitled) Register's Office mortgage certificate Frank Gass, County Register, 1908 (Inventory 3)
    Shows that the mortgage was paid off.
  - (untitled) Report on decline in membership John Price Jones Company, Consultants, 1954 (Inventory 4)
    Includes opinion poll.
  - (untitled) Title Search city/county clerks, 1879 (Inventory 5)
  - (untitled) Title Search city/county clerks, 1887 (Inventory 6)
  - 1844 Medal Event medal, Undated (Inventory 7)
  - 1844 Medal Event invitation, 2000 (Inventory 8)
  - 1844 Medal Event invitation and program, 1999 (Inventory 9)
  - 1844 Medal Event invitation and program, 2001 (Inventory 10)
  - 1844 Medal Event invitation and program, 2002 (Inventory 11)
  - 1844 Medal Event invitation and program, 2003 (Inventory 12)
  - 1844 Medal Event Program, 1994 (Inventory 13)
  - Abstract of the Title of Prison Association of New York Eugene Smith, Attorney, 1887 (Inventory 14)
    Contains all history of the building.
  - Abstract of the Title of Prison Association of New York (copy) Eugene Smith, Attorney 1887 (Inventory 15)
    Contains all history of the buildingm missing pages 25-65.
  - AIDS in Prison Project Update: A Medical Release Proposal, 1990 (Inventory 16)
  - Altered building application and other permits, 1983 (Inventory 17)
    Forms regarding request to turn basement into offices.
  - Annual Report 1894 Prison Association of New York (Inventory 18)
    Includes 50th anniversary information.
  - Annual Report 1946 Prison Association of New York (Inventory 19)
  - Annual Report 1990 (Inventory 20)
  - Annual Reports 1844-1845 Prison Association of New York (Inventory 21)
  - Annual Reports 1844-1846 Prison Association of New York (Inventory 22)
  - Annual Reports 1871-1874, vol. 9 Prison Association of New York (Inventory 23)
  - Annual Reports 1876-1886, vol. 10 Prison Association of New York (Inventory 24)
  - Annual Reports 1921-1922 Prison Association of New York (Inventory 25)
  - Annual Reports 1924-1929, vol. 25 Prison Association of New York (Inventory 26)
  - Annual Reports 1925-1927 Prison Association of New York (Inventory 27)
  - Annual Reports 1928-1929 Prison Association of New York (Inventory 28)
  - Annual Reports 1930-1931 Prison Association of New York (volume number is not marked) (Inventory 29)
  - Annual Reports 1930-1931, vol. 26 Prison Association of New York (Inventory 30)
  - Annual Reports 1932-1933, vol. 27 Prison Association of New York (Inventory 31)
  - Annual Reports 1932-1934 Prison Association of New York (Inventory 32)
  - Annual Reports 1934-1935 vol. 28 Prison Association of New York (Inventory 33)
  - Annual Reports 1935-1936 Prison Association of New York (Inventory 34)
  - Annual Reports 1936-1938, vol. 29 Prison Association of New York (Inventory 35)
  - Annual Reports 1937-1939 Prison Association of New York (Inventory 36)
  - Annual Reports 1939-1940, vol. 30 Prison Association of New York (Inventory 37)
  - Annual Reports 1940-1941 Prison Association of New York (Inventory 38)
  - Annual Reports 1941-1942 Prison Association of New York (Inventory 39)
  - Annual Reports 1942-1943 Prison Association of New York (Inventory 40)
  - Annual Reports 1943-1944 Prison Association of New York (Inventory 41)
  - Annual Reports 1944-1945 Prison Association of New York (Inventory 42)
  - Annual Reports 1945-1946 Prison Association of New York 1945-1946 (Inventory 43)
  - Annual Reports 1947-1948 Prison Association of New York (Inventory 44)